Not your average one night stand.
Contracted is a horror, thriller film directed by Eric England.
A young woman contracts what she believes to be an
STD—but it ends up being a far worse disease.
Samantha, played by Najarra Townsend.
Sam's Mom, played by Caroline Williams.
Nikki, played by Katie Stegeman.
Alice, played by Alice Macdonald.
Riley, played by Matt Mercer.
BJ, played by Simon Barrett.
Contracted is a 2013 American zombie-body horror independent
film written and directed by Eric England.
It was first released on November 23, 2013, in the United States and stars Najarra Townsend as a young woman
that finds herself suffering from a mysterious sexually transmitted disease after a rape.
It has been compared to the 2012 film
Thanatomorphose, with which it shares similarities.
Twitch Film has criticized the movie for its marketing, in which England
describes the character Samantha's rape as a "one night stand".
Some of the cast from the first film reprise their roles in the 2015 sequel,
Contracted: Phase II, written by Craig Walendziak and directed by Josh Forbes.
The film explores themes of rape, indoor plant, vomit, one-night stand, worm.
The tone is dark and intense.